<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Arshiya Ansari</title>
		<description>Data-driven, code-based</description>
		<link>https://arshiyaansari.github.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://arshiyaansari.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Basic Algorithm Patterns for Coding Interviews</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I hope to highlight some of the most common algorithm patterns I compiled while prepping for my coding interviews. When I first started prepping for coding interviews, I tended to &lt;em&gt;memorize&lt;/em&gt; the solutions for coding problems in the hopes that my interviewer would ask exactly the questions I studied. As you can guess, that never really happened so instead, I started to learn the patterns that are hidden in these problems so I could learn how to approach new problems – problems I’ve never seen before!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://arshiyaansari.github.io/technical/2020/10/19/algorithm-patterns.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://arshiyaansari.github.io/technical/2020/10/19/algorithm-patterns.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introductory blog post</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;My first introductory blog post begins with a reflection back on the journey that brought me here. In 2017, I made the biggest change of my life on my roommate’s twin-size mattress in the middle of the night. Dropping all of my pre-medical courses to pursue a computer science degree was something I never envisioned doing when I stepped on my college campus in 2016 — yet there I was! It just seemed like the best decision; it was written in my stars. In the next three years, I was immersed in a world so vibrant and evolving, I had never felt more at home. Through this blog, I hope to tell the story of my programming journey so it’ll help other people in tech find their footing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://arshiyaansari.github.io/personal/2020/09/09/first-post.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://arshiyaansari.github.io/personal/2020/09/09/first-post.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
